<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chuyu Tian</title>
    <link>http://chuyutian.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chuyu Tian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://chuyutian.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Channel</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/youtube/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to My YouTube Channel! This page provides an overview of my YouTube channel, dedicated to exploring the fascinating world of Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s ethics, virtue, and related philosophical concepts. We delve into his key ideas, analyze their relevance to contemporary issues, and offer insightful perspectives on living a good life.
All Videos Chuyu Tian&amp;rsquo;s YouTube Channel 
Feel free to subscribe to stay updated on new lectures and discussions!
Playlists and Featured Videos Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>For paper drafts or any questions, please reach me at ct2823@columbia.edu
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>A copy of my CV can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissertation</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/dissertation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/dissertation/</guid>
      <description>© 2025, Chuyu Tian The aim of my dissertation is to investigate the justificatory status of rules in Aristotle’s ethics. How does Aristotle’s ethics differ from a rule-based one? In my dissertation, I clarify the meta-ethical status of ethical judgments and investigate the foundation of Aristotle’s ethics.
In Chapter One, I propose a person-centric account of virtue and virtuous action. I argue that although Aristotle’s ethics involves rules, it differs fundamentally from rule-based ethics by beginning with the human being: the notion of the good person is necessary in defining virtue and action in accordance with virtue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
