<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chuyu Tian</title>
    <link>http://chuyutian.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chuyu Tian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://chuyutian.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/info/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/info/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please reach me at ct2823@columbia.edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/info/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/info/cv/</guid>
      <description>Here you can find my CV.
A copy of my CV can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/info/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/info/home/</guid>
      <description>I am a fifth year PhD student in Philosophy at Columbia University. My research focuses on Aristotle’s ethics, and includes such topics as: Aristotelian reasoning, akrasia, and particularism. I also have interests in classical East Asian and South Asian philosophy. Check out the menu bar to learn more about my research and teaching.
I grew up in Beijing and received my B.A. with honors from Northwestern University. In my spare time, I enjoy translating poems, visiting museums, painting and dancing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissertation</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/info/dissertation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/info/dissertation/</guid>
      <description>The aim of my dissertation is to investigate the justificatory status of rules in Aristotle’s ethics.
Based on Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s ethical corpus, I develop a model of ethical justification — a model where natural laws are summary of actions directly grounded by the good life, while conventional laws justify actions and are in turn justified by the good life — to offer a plausible explanation for the meta-ethical status of laws in Aristotle’s ethics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statement and CV</title>
      <link>http://chuyutian.com/info/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 09:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chuyutian.com/info/statement/</guid>
      <description>Photo Hello!
Academic Mission Statement I am a fourth year Ph.D. candidate in philosophy at Columbia University. I work mainly in Ancient philosophy and metaethics, with interest in Chinese philosophy. My dissertation aims to answer whether Aristotle is a particularist. I am also the rapporteur for the Neo-Confucianism Seminar at Columbia.
Contact Me Please reach me at ct2823@columbia.edu
CV A copy of my CV can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
